Holy Grail
压制:随Feng
歌名：Holy Grail  圣杯
歌手：Jay-Z feat. Justin Timberlake
Blue told me to remind you niggas
布鲁让我提醒黑鬼们
Fuck that shit y’all talk about
去他的 你们说的都是废话
I'm the nigga
我就是那黑鬼
Caught up in all these lights and cameras
交织在灯光与镜头间
But look what that shit did to Hammer
可是 瞧这东西对MC Hammer做了什么
God-damnit it I like it
该死 我就是喜欢这样
The bright lights is enticing
强光如此诱惑
But look what it did to Tyson
可是 瞧它对泰森做了什么
All that money in one night
一夜暴富
30 mill for one fight
一场拳击换下三千万美元
But soon as all the money blows, all the pigeons take flight
但只要钱财不再 白鸽自是逃离
Fuck the fame, keep cheating on me
该死的名声 一再出卖着我
What I do, I took her back, fool me twice
而我却把她带回身边 一再愚弄自己
That's my bad, I can't even blame her for that
都是我的错 我无法责怪她
Enough to make me wanna murder, Momma please just get my bail
这足以让我想谋杀 妈妈请让我保释
I know nobody to blame
我知道没有人可以怪罪
Kurt Cobain, I did it to myself
科特·柯本 我这样做是为了自己
And we all just entertainers
我们只是艺人
And we're stupid, and contagious
我们就是愚钝 具有传染性
And we all just entertainers
我们只是艺人
You take the clothes off my back
你褪下我的衣裳
And I let you
我不做声
You steal the food right out of my mouth
你从我嘴边窃取食物
And I watch you eat it
我看着你品尝
I still don't know why
我却依然不知
Why our love is so much
为何我们的爱如此深厚
Ohhh
You curse my name
你咒骂着我的姓名
In spite to put me to shame
让我羞愧难当
Air all my laundry in the streets
在大街小巷曝光我的衣物
Dirty or clean
不分净丑
Give it up for fame
为名声欢呼喝彩
But I still don't know why
但我却依然不知为何
Why I love it so much
我为何如此爱它
Yea
And Baby
宝贝
It's amazing I'm in this maze with you
不可思议的是 我和你却沦陷其中
I just can't crack the code
我仍然看不穿
One day you screaming you love me loud
有天你尖叫着爱我
The next day you're so cold
隔天却冷若寒冰
One day you here, one day you there, one day you care
你一天在这 一天在那 一天在乎
You're so unfair sipping from the cup
你是如此不公 端杯酌饮
Till it runneth over, Holy Grail
享受至极 圣杯
Now I got tattoos on my body
我带着纹身
Psycho bitches in my lobby
我心中神经质的婊子
I got haters in the paper
报纸上有恨我的
Photo shoots with paparazzi
和狗仔同照
Can't even take my daughter for a walk
却无法带女儿散步
See them by the corner store
在街角店遇见他们
I feel like I'm cornered off
我只觉被逼至绝路
Enough is enough
够了
I'm calling this off
我叫停
Who the fuck I'm kidding though?
我他妈在开谁的玩笑
I'm getting high
我正过瘾
Sitting low
低坐着
Sliding by
滑过人群
In that big body
在那硕大的车身里
Curtains all in my window
帷幕紧闭
This fame hurt
名声伤人
But this chain works
但这是必要的办法
I think back
我回想
You asked the same person
你曾问同一个人
If this is all you had to deal with
如果这就是你要面对的
Nigga deal with it
黑鬼处理好它
This shit ain't work
这是个糟糕的工作
This light work
聚灯光奏效
Camera snapping, my eyes hurt
镜头猛闪 刺痛了我的眼睛
Niggas dying back where I was birthed
黑鬼在出生之地渐渐死去
Fuck - your iris and IRS
去他的光环和国税局
Get the hell up off of your high horse
别给我高高在上
You got the shit that niggas die for
你拿走了黑鬼想要的
Dry yours
别玩假慈悲
Why you mad
为什么生气
Take the good with the bad
学着把好坏一并承受
Don't throw that baby out with the bath water
坏事里总有好事
You're still alive
你还活着
Still that nigga
仍旧是那个黑鬼
Niggas you survived
你仍旧存活着
You still getting bigger nigga
黑鬼 你还在成长
Living the life
生活着
Vanilla wafers
香草味酥饼
In a villa
在郊区别墅里
Illest nigga alive
病态黑鬼存活着
Michael Jackson thriller
迈克杰克逊的惊悚片
And Baby
宝贝
It's amazing I'm in this maze with you
不可思议的是 我和你却沦陷其中
I just can't crack the code
我仍然看不穿
One day you screaming you love me loud
有天你尖叫着爱我
The next day you're so cold
隔天却冷若寒冰
One day you here, one day you there, one day you care
你一天在这 一天在那 一天在乎
You're so unfair sipping from the cup
你是如此不公 端杯酌饮
Till it runneth over, Holy Grail
享受至极 圣杯
You get the air of my lungs whenever you need it
只要你想 你可以随时让我窒息
You take the blade right out of my heart just so you can watch me bleeding
将利刃从我的心口拔出 只为看我血流不止
I still don’t know why
我却依然不知
Why I love you so much
为何我的爱如此深厚
Don’t know why
不知道这是为什么
压制:随Feng